Guide to the Lee S. Shulman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- PAPERS BY OTHERS, Series 3
  - "Learning the Language of Practice," Robert Yinger, 1985 (research prospectus) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Everyone's Invited to the Party," Reynolds, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "The Conceptual Minefield of 'Structure': Meditations after Studying the Knowledge Structures of Student-Teachers," Phillips, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "On Teacher Knowledge: A Skeptical Dialogue," Phillips (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Why the Worry About Warrant Will Not Wane," Phillips, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "Teachers and Curricular Materials: Who is Driving Whom?" Reynolds, Haymore, Ringstaff, Grossman, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Research Proposal, Anna [Richert], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Unacknowledged Knowledge Growth: A Re-examination of the Effects of Teacher Education," Grossman, Richert, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Organization of Subject-Matter in Computer Programming Lessons," Baxter, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Knowledge Growth in Teaching: Research in Progress on Secondary School Teachers," Richert, Wilson, Marks, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - "Teacher Assessment and Professionalization," Tom Bird, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Quarrels with Myself: Mixed Reactions to the Holmes Group's Report," Tom Bird, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Social Inquiry by and for Earthlings," Cronbach [1986] (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "From Fieldwork to Class work," Wineburg, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Everyone's Invited to the Party," Reynolds, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Learning by Doing," Reynolds, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "The Anthropologist in the Classroom," McGraw, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Those Who Appreciate: The Mathematician as Secondary Teacher," Marks, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "From Successful Student to Frustrated Teacher," Haymore, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Math Teacher or English Teacher?" Haymore, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "A Passion for Language," Grossman, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "A Tale of Two Teachers: The Role of Subject Matter Orientation in Teaching," Grossman, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - "Conviction-That Granite Base," Grossman, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "A Practical Philosopher," Baxter, case study, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - "The Influence of Subject Matter Background on Planning and Instruction: An English Teacher and Science Teacher teach Cannery Row," Ringstaff, Haymore, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "Learning to Teach Social Studies: Case Studies of Chris and Cathy," Gudmundsdottir, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Pedagogical Content Knowledge: Teacher's Ways of Knowing," Gudmundsdottir, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "Peering at History…," Wilson and Wineburg, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "Reflection and Pedagogical Caring…," Richert, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - "Teacher Misassignment…," Ringstaff, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "Teachers and Texts…," Grossman and Gudmundsdottir, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "Planting Seeds: The Use of Case Studies in the Generation and Elaboration of Theory," Grossman, Wilson, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "Elementary Teachers' Pedagogical Content Knowledge in Mathematics," dissertation proposal, Marks, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Learning to Teach Without Teacher Education," draft, Grossman, 1988. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "Subject Matter Knowledge in the Teaching of History," Wineburg and Wilson, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "Models of Wisdom in the Teaching of History," Winesburg and Wilson, [ca. 1988] (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "Graduate Education and Research Imperatives: Views from Campuses in the United States," Gunport, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - "Models of the Learner," Jerome Bulter, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - "Research on Student's Conceptions in Science: An Analytic Perspective," [author unknown], n.d. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Papers by Others, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Proposals by Others, etc. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Proposals by Others, etc. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Proposals by Others, etc. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, Proposals by Others, etc. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- COURSE WORK/CASE STUDIES, Series 4
  - "Epistemological Foundations of Cognitive Psychology," course reader by Lee Shulman (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Epistemological Foundations of Cognitive Psychology," course reader by Lee Shulman, cont. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Epistemological Foundations of Cognitive Psychology," course reader by Lee Shulman, copy 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Epistemological Foundations of Cognitive Psychology," course reader by Lee Shulman, copy 2 cont. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Notes re. Epistemological Foundations (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Epistemological Foundations of Cognitive Psychology, Course reader, Shulman (Text sections) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Education 811 [ca. 1972] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Education 911A: Overview, [ca. 1973] (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Education 911 Proposals, Winter term, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Education 911: Winter 1976, Papers (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Education 911: Fall, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Education 911: Winter, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Education 911: Fall, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Education 911: Course material, Winter, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Education 911: Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Education 912 [ca. 1977-1978] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Education 982: Spring, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Education 982: Course Readings/notes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Education 982: 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Education 982: notes, ca. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Education 982: articles and handouts (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Education 982: Research on Teaching (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Education 169: Case studies, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Education 232A: course reader, Fall 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Education 232A: notes re. course reader, Fall 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Education 269 Casebook: 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: biology (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: geography (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: English and Social Studies (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: Current events (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: World History and Culture (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: U.S. History and Politics (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: Algebra and Trigonometry (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: Geometry (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: Cultural and Equity themes in Literature (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: writing and grammar, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: Literature (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: French and German (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: science, atomic structure/computers (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Education 269 case studies, 1991: Spanish (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Education 269, 1991: reciprocal observations (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Education 269, 1991: reciprocal observations (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Education 269, 1991: reciprocal observations (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Education 269, 1991: reciprocal observations (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Education 269, 1991: reciprocal observations (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Education 269, 1991: case studies (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Education 269 casebook, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Education 269: case report release forms, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Education 269 course reader, Winter 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Education 269: syllabus, requirements, releases/agreements, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Education 269: course reader, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Education 269: course reader, 1996 cont. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Education 269: student case studies, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Education 269: Case study reproduction agreements with case study, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Education 269: Case studies, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Education 269: Course Reader (sections A-C), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Education 269: Course Reader (section D), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Education 269: miscellaneous syllabi, notes, 1987-2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Education 271: Introduction to Systems, Issues and Problems in Education Research, Fall 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Education 271: Syllabus, Fall 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Education 271: Course Readings (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Education 271: Selected Readings (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Education 302x: student case studies, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Education 302x: student case studies, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - [Education 302]: STEP case reader, June 1992 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - [Education 302]: STEP case reader, June 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Education 302: Prospective Principals Program, casebook, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Education 302: Prospective Principals Program, casebook, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Education 302: Course Reader, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Education 302: Course Reader, 1997, cont. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Education 302: Course Reader notes (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Education 302: Course Reader, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Education 302x: case studies, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Education 302x: case studies, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Education 302x: case studies, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Education 317: Research on Teaching, Spring 1988/89 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Education 317: 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Education 317: Course Reader, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Education 317: Course Reader, 1993, cont. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Education 317: 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Education 317 course reader, Spring 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Education 317 course reader, Spring 1995 (cont.) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Education 317 course reader, Spring 1995 (cont.) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Education 317: Miscellaneous Education teaching material, Shulman (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Education 321: 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Education 321: Course Reader (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Education 347: Course Reader, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Education 347: Course Reader, 1996, cont. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Education 347: Course Reader notes (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Theory, Practice, and the Education of Professionals," 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Case studies: no date (Box 13, Folder 7)
- PROJECTS, Series 5
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): General Elementary (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): General Junior High (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Anastopolis, Mary (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Becker, Judith (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Burns, Allen (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Ellenby, Gloria (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Engh, Robert (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Esposito, Vincent (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Gorman, Howard (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Grier, Rosalie (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Mellor, Edward (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Rogers, Fred (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Rollins, Adele (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Serota, Catherine (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Simson, John (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Torres, James (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Washington, Deanna (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Red Oak Study (ca.1965-1968): Zenner, Gloria (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanford and the Schools, Teacher Education Project, 1983 (Project Statement) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Practice interviews among interviewers, [1983] (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Interviews with experienced teachers, [1983] (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Interviews of STEP students, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Interviews by STEP students, [1983] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dinner meeting transcript re. STEP program interviews [1983] (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Spencer Study: protocols, instruments, materials (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Spencer Project: planning, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Spencer Project: planning, 1984 (cont.) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Interview parameters, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Spencer correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Science protocols (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Subjects (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Spencer Instruments (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Spencer - Annotated Bibliography (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - STEP interview with Alice, Intellectual Biography, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - STEP interview with Alice,: English (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - STEP interview with Arnold (English), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - [South City] interviews with Bryan, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - South City interviews with Catherine, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - South City interviews with Catherine, 1984-1985 (cont.) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - STEP interviews with Cathy (Social Studies), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - STEP interviews with Chris (Social Studies), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - STEP interviews with Chris (Social Studies), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Interview with Colleen (English), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Colleen's data - English (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - STEP Interview with Daniel (English), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - STEP interviews with Debi (English), 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - South City interviews with Frank, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - STEP interviews with Fred (Social Studies), 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - [South City] interviews with Gail, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - George's data (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - UC Berkeley interview with Jill (English), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - UC Berkeley interview with Joe (Math), 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Joe's data: Math (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - STEP interviews with Laura (Math), 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - STEP interviews with Laura (Math), 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Laura's data (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - South City interviews with Lewis, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - South City interviews with Lewis, 1984-1985, cont. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lewis (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - South City interviews with Mark, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - STEP interviews with Martha (English), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - STEP interviews with Martha (English), 1984-1985 (cont.) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - UC Berkeley interview with Patrece (Science), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Patrece: interview/transcripts (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Patrece Patterson Observations (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - STEP interviews with Scott (Math), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - STEP interviews with Scott (Math), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - STEP interviews with Sharon (Math), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sharon's data: Math (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "Steve" (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - STEP interview with Teresa (Social Studies), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - South City interviews with Yvonne, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - South City interviews with Yvonne, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - STEP interview transcripts, administrative, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - South City administrative and faculty interviews, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - UC Berkeley staff interviews, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Math Supervisor Interview, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Interview Transcripts (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - PCKI: Math (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - CPCK data: Math (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - PCK data: Math (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - PCKSM: Math (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - PCKS: Math (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - PCKS Data: English (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - CPCK data: English (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - PCKI data: English (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Spencer: Miscellaneous data (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Spencer data (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Science: All (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Science Paper - Spencer (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - B-site interviews - Judy (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - B-site interviews - Gary (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Site reports: October 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Valley College" report (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Valley College Pilot Year Report" (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Bellman University" report (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "Bay College" report (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Science Group (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Comments by Spencer Informants (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Spencer Documents/Comments/Observations (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Jill Royster's Observations (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correction/Comments to Spencer Papers (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Publications File (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lee Shulman: Spencer Project, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Analysis- [Math Teaching], unidentified, 1985/86 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Observation, September 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Spencer Project Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Research Group Notes from meeting, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Toward a Pedagogy of Substance, Spencer Project, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Spencer Project, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Spencer Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Spencer Project: Proposal information, expenditure reports, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Expense statements - Ford, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Spencer Project: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Knowledge Growth in a Profession," November 14, 1983 (Proposal to the Spencer Foundation); "Knowledge Growth in Teaching: A Final Report to the Spencer Foundation," [ca. 1987] (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Spencer: Group meeting agenda, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Case study reports (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cohort study and other materials from John Boli (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mills Project: transcript interview with Karen, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Mills Project: transcript interviews with Elena, Anna, Renee, Max, Jason, Jean, Karin, Edna, Rich, and Peter (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Spencer: summary sheets; cover letter (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ford Foundation Proposal: "The Quality of Undergraduate Education," March 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Knowledge Growth: Human subjects (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - San Jose: Materials and Information (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - San Jose: Transcripts: Program Info.; Admin/Fac. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Spencer: transparencies (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Spencer Bookeeping, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Papers from the Spencer project (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Spencer budget (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation: expense reports (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Ford miscellaneous: expense reports, correspondence, etc.1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Budget originals (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Spencer: transcripts and interviews (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Spencer: case study group meetings (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Spencer: South City Teacher Education Program Information, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Michigan State Information (KULT project) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Spring quarter protocols, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Spencer notes from Ruth at end of year (1985) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Report from the STEP Site," Carey, Gudmundsdottir, Wilson, June 1984 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Protocols and Reports: Spencer methodology, July 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Themes and Quotes: Spencer and technical reports (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Spencer Project: general info. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Lynn Mulkey (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - CSU Planning Conference, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Large Group Meetings and interesting ideas, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Interview questions (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Sites' Reports, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Consent sheets of students (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - STEP consent forms (originals and with signatures) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - English (subject matter group) - Protocols (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Social Studies (subject matter group) - Protocols (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Math (subject matter group) - Protocols (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Prep sheets (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Teacher Knowledge Research (SATS Teacher Education), ca. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Spencer Meeting notes, 5/13/1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Spencer Project: miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Spencer Project: miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie Forum II: Lee presenting, San Diego, May 1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Trudy: interviews I - II, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Trudy: interviews III - IV, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Homework and Short Cuts Pilot, 1987 (1) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Homework and Short Cuts Pilot, 1987 (2) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Pilot Tests: Videotape Topic Sequence, Math (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Draft Interview Protocol, Math, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Carol Wilson, 1986 (interviews I-II) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Carol Wilson, 1986 (interviews III-IV) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Christopher Williams, 1986 (interview I) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Christopher Williams, 1986 (interview II) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Christopher Williams: Resource Packet (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Math, 1986 (1) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Math, 1986 (2) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Math, 1986 (3) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Math, 1986 (4) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Math, 1986 (5) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Social Studies, interview I, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Social Studies, interview II, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Wisdom of Practice Interviews, Social Studies, interview III-IV, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Protocols: Life Interview - Teacher Summaries, May 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Protocols: Preliminary Information, September 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Protocols: First Interviews, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Protocols: Second Interviews, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Protocols: Third Interviews, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Carnegie Protocols: Fourth - Fifth Interviews, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - David Rhodes: History Teacher Assessment (1), 1987-1988 (training packet) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - David Rhodes: History Teacher Assessment (2), 1987-1988 (training packet) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - David Rhodes: History Teacher Assessment (3), 1987-1988 (training packet) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Joan Elston: Math Teacher Assessment, [ca. 1987-1988] (training packet) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Maureen Hansen: Math Teacher Assessment, ca. 1987 (training packet) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Jane Risk: TFL scoring exercises, Math, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Jane Risk, scoring feedback (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Eleanor Rosenast: scoring protocols, Math, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dolly Travers: scoring protocols, Literacy, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)